MkvDrama.net
You’re finally awake.
Maggie?
Hey! Are you okay?
The person behind your abduction
is someone who reeks of evil and relentless manipulation.
Welcome to the White Hostel!
You think, you can already play the role of Janine’s boyfriend?
I didn't mean to!
I let myself in.
I hope you don’t mind.
My name is Luthor...
Mendez.
Loki’s elder brother.
It seems like your club is busy attending to new clients.
I let myself in.
That's enough, Maggie!
I hope you don’t mind.
Forgive my manners.
I haven't introduced myself properly.
My name is Luthor...
Mendez.
Loki’s elder brother.
Luthor.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lorelei.
Nice to meet you, Lorelei.
What the hell?
Did you let this guy inside our clubroom?
If not...
did he materialize out of thin air?
Or did he emerge out of the pentagram?
Look, look. I'm sorry. Okay?
First of all, I had no idea he was your brother.
Secondly, I didn’t know that’s how you’d react.
Look, for all we know,
he might bring up a case.
Case?
Turns out there’s a case
even a master manipulator like you can’t handle.
With all those resources and schemes up your sleeve?
You disappoint me.
I’m just preoccupied with other things.
Besides...
the problem that I will refer to you requires an outsider’s hand.
We don’t accept suspicious requests.
So leave.
Did you forget that I'm the chairman of the committee
of non-mandated organizations?
Even if you haven’t met the minimum number of members,
your renewal still got approved.
So, yeah, I would expect for you to show a little bit of gratitude
by doing us a favor.
If you don’t want, it’s easy to reverse the decision.
The Paranormal Club seems to fit in here.
You know they've been requesting for this clubroom for ages.
I told you before that he’s despicable, didn’t I?
So should we discuss my request
or should I leave now and revoke your club’s status?
♪ Shadows ♪
♪ in the dark are crawling ♪
♪ Keeping watch and barring your way ♪
♪ As if the line could not be crossed ♪
♪ To every scream and every tremor ♪
♪ These walls remain the only witness ♪
♪ Every noise is etched in here ♪
♪ Like fire and ammunition for your memory ♪
♪ Heed the warnings ♪
♪ The threats poised to strike ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined ♪
♪ Heed the warnings ♪
♪ Open up your eyes ♪
♪ For this world ♪
♪ is not what you imagined ♪
♪ Heed the warnings ♪
This is a confidential matter.
A friend of mine is being blackmailed by another student.
Is it really a friend?
Or maybe one of your pawns?
A student named Charles Meliton,
he has compromising photographs of my friend.
And he won't release those,
unless we pay him 3,000 pesos per photo.
How did he get those photos?
That’s what we don’t know.
But we’re hundred percent certain that he has them.
This is not the first time
that Charles tried to extort money from another student.
We received multiple reports telling the same story.
I guess you could call him a serial blackmailer.
Loki...
I think we should take on this case.
No one deserves to have their compromising photos exposed
without their consent.
So...
what do you want us to do?
Beg him to stop blackmailing your so-called friend and other students?
I want you to retrieve the storage device containing the said photos
along with everything that he’s got on the other students.
That’s where he gets his confidence.
You take that away from him, he'd lose leverage.
Why can’t you solve this petty problem on your own?
You have plenty of resources as part of the student council.
You’re just wasting your time asking us.
Because Charles knows every officer
in the student council and executive committee.
His awareness of us makes any move from our side,
I guess, risky?
If he finds out we’re planning something,
he might get triggered and upload the files.
That’s why it has to be you.
A third party
who is not under the influence of the council.
I'll have someone bring you the files that we have on Charles.
I hope that you can come up with a plan
to end his villainy by tomorrow.
If you pull this off,
consider us even.
And as for you, Lorelei...
I’d like to get to know you better.
Maybe we can have a chat over tea sometime.
Hey! What are you doing?
Hello?
Earth to Loki.
Feels like I have no one to talk to.
I’d rather sit here for now.
But I need to get a new chair.
I can still feel his eerie presence
just by staring at that chair.
Why are you that angry at your brother?
Lorelei...
you’ll never understand.
He's not your brother.
You never told me your brother is actually the VP of the student council.
Actually...
he's not just the Vice President of the student council.
He is the student council.
The President is just a puppet.
It’s my brother pulling the strings.
That’s why
if ever he invites you to a tea party...
decline his offer.
Or ignore his invitation completely.
Hello?
Can we help you?
That was weird.
What's that?
So this is what Charles Meliton looks like.
To be fair, he looks innocent.
Looks like he wouldn’t do something like that.
Like what they say,
looks can be deceiving.
Some wolves hide very well in sheep’s clothing.
This is all we need.
The rest can be disregarded.
We have to time this perfectly.
We can’t just approach him
while he has class.
But...
it's too risky to ambush him during his break.
How about during his P.E. class?
P.E. class.
P.E. class is the best time to ambush him
since he’ll definitely be changing in the locker room.
Here’s the plan.
You’re the one going in the locker room,
and I’ll be your lookout outside.
Aren’t you good at lockpicking?
Opening his locker should be easy for you.
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Why did I just do that?
Oh, no, no, no. He's coming.
Let's go.
So, did you see anything?
He wouldn't be leaving something as important as that.
Maybe it’s in his pocket?
I don’t think so.
He wouldn’t keep that in his pocket during P.E. class.
If it's a flash drive,
he might lose it.
If it’s an external hard drive,
it would be inconvenient for him.
But look what I’ve found
in his bag.
Did he know we’d do this,
so he put that there?
I don’t think so.
By the looks of it,
the paper looks old.
Seems like it’s been there for a while.
So, what do we do?
What I’m wondering is,
why didn’t Charles bring his phone?
How did you know that?
I didn’t see a phone in his bag.
I’ve been observing him
and I haven’t seen him take out his phone not even once.
It’s impossible that he doesn’t have his own phone nowadays.
So, does that mean he left it at home?
That’s my theory.
Okay. Well, so what's our plan?
It’s time for Plan B.
Do you know where Carl lives?
Charles!
It’s Charles, Loki.
Charles.
Well, I got this.
Meet me at the White Hostel, 5 p.m.
Yes, Ms. Rios?
Ma’am,
I think I’m feeling a bit dizzy.
Are you okay?
May I go to the clinic?
Okay, Ms. Rios. You’ll be excused.
Lori, do you want me to come with you?
No, I’ve got this.
But you said...
Rosetta, I’ve got this.
I’m feeling really dizzy.
Ma’am, I think I’m starting to feel dizzy too.
Ms. Rodriguez, take your seat.
Loki.
What took you so long?
Did you forget that we were supposed to meet at 5 p.m.?
It’s already 5:10.
I just came from my Humanities class.
I kind of just ran off.
Humanities?
That's just a minor subject.
Why on earth would you prioritize a subject
that probably won’t even matter to your future career
over coming here on time?
- Excuse... - You had me waiting for ten minutes!
Fine! Okay. I’m sorry.
There’s our target.
Ma'am, sir, are you staying here?
Sir, don’t you remember me?
Ah, you’re ma’am Rosetta’s friend?
You’re the ones who solved the case last week?
Yes, that was us.
Actually, I’m just visiting my friend again.
Alright, ma’am. Just log in.
Third floor, please?
We need to figure out a way to get in and grab Charles’ phone.
What if we just wait for him to come out again?
Then just lockpick the door so we can go inside.
We might be waiting in vain.
We’re not sure if he’ll come out again.
Lorelei, we have to do something.
Charles just went live.
Hi, guys! So today, it’s ramen time!
Not the instant kind,
I had real ramen delivered.
This guy surely is full of himself.
Imagine, livestreaming on your own while eating.
Talk about narcissism.
At least we know that he’s alone in the room.
And we know where to get his phone.
We can’t wait for him.
We’ll make him come out of his hole.
Wait! Where are you going?
What was that? Come on, go outside!
He left his phone!
He’s still on a livestream.
Great!
I’ll get what we need from the room.
Keep an eye out for me.
What?
Affirmative.
Fire! Good thing there’s no fire!
What’s wrong with you? Watch where you’re going. Idiot.
Sorry, I didn’t notice you.
Your sorry means nothing, you already hit me.
Good thing you’re pretty.
All the compromising photos and files are here.
I turned off the phone's tracking device, so he can't locate it.
We'll handle this...
including whatever sanction we decide to give him.
Do you need anything else?
Maybe it’s too much to expect a thank you from you.
You can’t even say the magic word.
Loki...
this is simply your payment for us not dissolving your club.
As I said, do us this favor and we’re even.
Is that clear?
Now that our debt is settled,
you can stay away from us.
We...
definitely don’t enjoy your company!
Well, unfortunately, I’m quite sure that we will be crossing paths again.
Even if we don’t want to.
You don’t need to include this case in the Chronicles.
Got it.
Just remember what I told you about Luthor.
Don’t get involved with him as much as possible.
It’s for your own good.
Crazy what happened at White Hostel yesterday, right?
They’re now investigating who pressed the alarm.
Hey, Lorelei.
Go on, Rosetta. You should get to class.
Congratulations on another case closed,
though I heard that you stirred up quite a scene at the hostel.
What do you want now?
Don’t tell me you’ve already fallen for him?
How pitiful.
Just because I help Loki on investigations
doesn’t mean I have feelings for him.
And one more thing, it’s none of your business.
I thought you said you’d stop bothering me.
I did say that I wouldn’t bother you anymore.
But that doesn’t mean we won’t see each other again.
So what do you really want?
I’m just here to deliver a message.
The vice president wants to meet you.
Just remember what I told you about Luthor.
Don’t get involved with him as much as possible.
Why?
Aren’t you interested to know more about him?
Don’t you wanna know why Loki hates him so much?
Just be at the cafeteria later at 8 p.m. if you want to meet him.
Okay?
Madonna, we’re leaving.
Aren’t you coming?
I’ll go later. I still need to memorize this.
You’re taking that too seriously.
I have to.
I want to get the lead role in the auditions.
You know Jamie’s the theater club moderator’s favorite.
For now.
But once they see how good I am,
I’m sure Jamie’s crown will be mine.
Okay, Madonna. Good luck!
We’re going ahead, okay?
Alright, go!
Good luck, girl. You can do it!
- You can definitely do it! - Thank you! Thank you, guys!
Make sure you watch, okay?
- Yes. Of course! - Of course, girl!
Do your best!
- Of course! - Bye!
Thank you!
That one’s all yours!
I know! Come on, go.
Hello, Lorelei.
Hello, Luthor.
Please…
sit.
Thank you for meeting me this late.
The cafeteria should be closed
but I pulled some strings, so we could have our meeting here.
Are you sure you don’t want some tea or coffee?
I still have a lot to do.
Can we make this quick?
Very well.
I’m sorry for having you abducted.
We had to resort to such methods
since you refused to leave the club that my brother is so fond of.
We also wanted to test his resolve
to see if he would come to your rescue if you would be put in any danger.
So Loki was right.
You're the mastermind.
Tell me,
why are you forcing me to leave the Q.E.D. Club?
What's going on?
Why are you so obsessed with it?
Maggie must have told you repeatedly that she wants to help you.
The truth is...
we are just trying to protect you
from any danger that might come with your association with my brother.
You know Rhea, right?
And you know what happened to her.
Yes.
Loki said
she was killed
by someone known only as "M."
And why would they kill an innocent girl?
Because he was close to Loki.
Every collision has collateral damage, Lorelei.
More than half a year ago,
my brother investigated several cases that connected all to one person…
only known as "M."
And this elusive M seemingly struck back,
by killing my brother’s only friend.
Rhea became that collateral damage.
So…
what does that have to do with you kidnapping me?
That M is still active.
And you, by being Loki’s closest person…
could be the next collateral damage.
We are trying to prevent that.
I personally ask Maggie to persuade you to leave the club.
But it seems like you don’t want to.
Looks like you’re willing to take the risk for Loki.
I wonder why.
Well,
if I end up as collateral damage,
don’t you think,
I should be ready for whatever happens to me,
right?
Loki loves mysteries,
and you are a mystery to him, Lorelei.
He doesn’t see you as a person.
He sees you as a puzzle that he needs to solve.
I was thinking that it's possible
that the both of you are seeking to escape a tragic past.
See, Loki lost someone important in his life.
And I was wondering, what about you?
What happened in your previous school?
Is there anything that happened?
I can see why your brother gets annoyed with you.
You think you know better than any of us.
So what?
You think that…
you can control all of our decisions and fix our actions
that you deem as mistakes.
Lorelei, I can assure you that is not my intention.
If you say so.
Now if you’ll excuse me,
I have to get going.
One more thing, Lorelei…
this is just a hunch.
But Loki might use you as a bait
to lure out M.
Just like cheese on a mouse trap.
I hope I’m wrong.
Hey! You guys are OA!
Seriously…
you're just messing with me.
Is anyone around?
These guys...
OA! OA!
Tell me the truth!
Am I no longer the one your heart beats for?
Tell me the truth.
Is there someone else who owns you now?
If that's the case,
I promise you...
you’ll never see me again.
You’ll never see me again for the rest of your life!
Goodbye.
Hello?
Who’s that?
Hey, you guys again! So OA!
Now you’re even scaring me. You guys, seriously!
Enough with the prank! Enough with the prank!
Loki?
Is that you?
What are you doing here?
I decided to, you know, finish some work at the Q.E.D. Club.
And decided to wait for you.
Going home?
Mm-hmm.
Something wrong?
Seems like your mind’s roaming around the cosmic space.
Can I ask something?
Yeah, sure.
I hope it’s a life-changing question.
Are you hungry?
That’s it?
No...
No hypothetical,
existential,
or metaphysical query?
Nothing.
Because I’ve been hungry for a while now.
I was just wondering.
We can buy food.
Okay.
Yup.
This is just a hunch.
Loki might use you as bait to lure out M.
I hope I’m wrong.
How’s it going?
The OSA has decided to suspend me for a week
because of the commotion I caused at the White Hostel the other day.
But they took it back right away.
My sibling worked some magic, so the suspension was lifted.
It’s a good thing.
I can’t imagine the clubroom if you get suspended.
I won’t be able to take clients,
or solve cases by myself.
Even if I get suspended,
I still be in the clubroom no matter what.
Classes are the only thing I can’t go to.
But I can still manage…
club affairs.
And to be frank…
I prefer being suspended.
So that I wouldn’t have to pretend to listen to my boring instructors.
I hope, at least, you learned something from what happened.
Also, I think you should thank your brother.
If it weren’t for him,
you probably wouldn’t have been able to attend class.
Why should I?
The student council, through him, asked for our help.
It’s their duty to cover our asses!
They should be the one thanking us,
not the other way around.
By the way,
I found out the one being blackmailed is a student council officer.
Really?
You’ll be surprised to know…
that Charles Meliton is connected
to a problem brought to us by another client.
Do you remember that poor girl
who wore skirt some inches abover her knees?
Madonna Barcelon?
The one betrayed by her friend?
Maybe they’re just jealous of my beauty?
Madonna, you go, girl!
That one.
How are the two cases connected?
He was the one who blackmailed Malena’s friend,
to feed him embarrassing information to our ex-client.
You mean Madonna, right?
Apparently, someone ordered him to find dirt on the student council
in exchange of embarasssing photos.
So, there’s a third party involved?
Who?
He doesn’t know the identity of this anonymous source.
They only communicate online,
and the account they use is a dummy email.
Excuse me.
Am I disturbing you?
If you’re busy, I’ll just come back later.
No, not really! Please, have a seat.
Do you have a case to consult or bring to us?
How can we help you?
I'm Geneva.
My classmate is missing.
I’m sure you know her, since she’s asked for your help before.
Sorry, but we’ve already helped a lot.
Who are you talking about?
It’s Madonna Barcelon.
Madonna and I are dormmates.
She didn’t go home last night.
I even went to the theater because I knew she’d be practicing there.
I even went back to get my dorm keys…
because I forgot.
She said she’d just be home late.
But she never made it home.
She didn’t even call or text me.
Well, how can you conclude that she’s missing based on that?
Maybe she went to one of her many suitors.
But she didn’t go to class earlier.
I called her phone several times, but it’s out of coverage area.
I asked the guys she might’ve gone to,
but Madonna didn’t contact any of them.
Didn’t anyone actually see her leave campus?
I asked the guards and showed her photo
if they noticed Madonna leaving,
but they didn’t see her.
I already reported everything to campus police.
But I think it’ll take a while to solve the case
because they’ve got a lot of work.
That’s why I decided to come to you.
Well...
I’m not interested in this one.
This case is not worth our time.
Once it’s confirmed that she’s missing,
you can return to us or leave this case to the campus police.
Loki!
Are you sure Madonna didn’t go anywhere else?
She always tells me
or texts me when she’s going somewhere.
But this time, she didn’t say anything or even give a sign.
Until it is proven that your friend is indeed missing,
this case is not worth our time.
If you think Madonna’s not really missing, let’s prove it to Geneva.
Isn’t that what Q.E.D. is all about?
Helping people! Right?
Fine!
We’ll prove that your friend isn’t missing
and she shouldn’t be worried about her.
I’m going to call the campus security office.
They owe me big time,
so I'm sure they’ll let me check yesterday’s footage.
We’ll see Madonna leave school,
and check if she’s with someone.
What time did you last see her on campus?
Around quarter to 5?
There’s only one campus exit and entrance,
so we could immediately see if she left.
Can we check that again?
Told you, she didn’t leave the campus.
Isn’t there any other secret exit Madonna could’ve used?
Nothing, ma’am.
Is he still the one on duty?
Yes, sir. It’s still Muldong.
This is a thrilling case after all!
If Madonna really didn’t leave,
she must still be on campus.
She could’ve been slain in one of the rooms.
And this might be a missing corpse case.
Loki, come on!
We’re going to find her. Okay?
Hello, sir?
I’m the one who asked you earlier this morning.
I just want to confirm, did you really not see my friend?
There’s no way I’d forget this, she’s gorgeous.
I have a sharp memory, I’ll recognize her right away.
Are missing students a thing now?
Are there any other missing students?
Yes.
The campus police officers came here.
They’re asking if I saw any students, two girls.
They’re asking if I saw them leave the building on Monday and Tuesday.
I saw them go in, but I didn’t see them come out.
Too bad, they were actually really nice.
I hope their parents find them soon.
I have some questions.
First,
we saw you leave your desk at 7 p.m.
Where did you go at that time?
That’s part of our job.
To double-check the students,
if they’ve already left.
We also check every room
to see if there were any students left.
I checked all the floors.
On the 5th floor, where the theater is…
did you notice anything unusual?
Not really.
Do you always do rounds?
Since I was on duty Sunday, yes.
Didn’t you notice anything unusual on any of the floors?
On one room on the 4th floor,
the door won’t stay shut.
No matter how I close it, it keeps opening.
And on the basement, by the anatomy room,
there’s always a foul smell.
Sometimes, I feel like there’s someone there.
But when I peek in, there’s nothing.
I didn't inspect it at all.
Because I'm scared I might see a real corpse.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thanks, chief.
What did chief say?
Apparently, they already know about the missing female students’ cases.
But they still don’t have a lead.
The other girls missing are named Mylene Canlas and Michelle De Guzman.
They already searched the campus a few days ago
but they found no corpse
or trace if either or both are dead.
It doesn’t look like a kidnapping for ransom,
because no one’s contacting their parents.
There’s a high chance it’s murder.
But where could their bodies be?
Could this be a case of serial killing?
It seems like there’s a pattern.
Mylene, Michelle, Madonna.
They all disappeared, like magic.
You’re probably right, Lorelei.
The person behind these incidents
must have used magic to make them disappear.
Are you serious?
There’s another case that maybe connected to this one.
Do you remember the chemistry lab case?
According to Chief Estrada,
the missing chemical compounds in the lab
are Sodium Hydroxide.
At first, I was clueless as to why someone would steal them.
Then I realized that it could make the disappearance happen as if by magic.
Sorry, I’m not good at chemistry.
What’s that for?
It’s used as a drain cleaner.
You pour that chemical down the drain
to remove human hair clogging the pipes.
It can also be used to melt bodies.
Human bodies.
Give it a few hours
and it will leave no trace
except for teeth
and nails.
Now...
guess who might be behind all these intertwined mysteries?
Someone who asked Genesis
to steal botttles of sodium hydroxide from the lab.
And someone who was disappointed that Madonna Barcelon’s image
wasn’t totally ruined by her dirty secret.
Someone who decided to use a brutal yet clean method
to dispose of a person who they deemed a nuisance.
M?
Judging by how almost flawless these incidents are,
only M could be the one behind it.
But I don’t believe in perfect crimes
because those who commit them are humans.
Prone to errors and imperfections.
He might have committed some mistakes along the way
that would lead us to them.
I'm thrilled to solve this case.
And I realized something.
He wants to send me a message,
that’s why all the victims’ names start with M.
That M would do anything just to get on my nerves.
If it really is him,
I hope we’re not too late.
I hope we can still find the missing ones.
Loki, I’ll go ahead.
I still have class.
Just text me if there are any new updates about the case.
How about you? Aren’t you going to class?
I'll probably skip them today so I can work on this case.
Mylene and Michelle were last seen on campus around 5 p.m.
Mylene was last seen in room 205 where her last class was.
Michelle was last seen in the English clubroom
before she disappeared.
Meanwhile, Madonna was in the auditorium.
I went to every room but there were no traces of blood.
So, is this like Janine’s case,
where they knew the culprit and went voluntarily?
Unlikely. They don't have a single common friend.
How did the culprit move the victims without anyone noticing?
Maybe we should ask Chief Estrada for help in the search.
No. If M is involved, I don't want to involve the police.
M is mine.
Excuse me?
We have an activity going on. Please give me that phone.
Sorry, ma’am. It’s important.
You can have it back after class.
Please?
Loki, please pick up.
Sorry! Sorry! I’m just in a hurry.
Oh, come on.
What's this?
Pick up the phone. Come on.
Loki, why...
Oh, sorry.
Wait,
why do you seem familiar?
John Bautista?
John Bautista, secretary.
- What did you do to Isaac, huh? - John, believe me!
But why are you dressed as a janitor?
Help!
You?
You’re the one who abducted them?
Yeah, it’s me!
And now it’s your turn.
Looks like we need to teach that guy a lesson again.
Let’s see if he still won’t learn from this.
She's awake.
I don’t want to die yet!
I want to achieve my dreams.
I still want to get to know Loki and myself.
I admire your survival instincts, for a woman.
I only knew him as “M,” that’s it.
He’s everywhere, Lorelei.
He's got eyes and ears everywhere.
Moriya! Moriarty!
Moriarity is a professor of Mathematics,
known as “the Napoleon of crime."
The mastermind behind half of the evil in the world.